<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Implementation on Eclipse KUKSA</title>
    <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/categories/implementation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Implementation on Eclipse KUKSA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/categories/implementation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Security Audit for Eclipse Kuksa released</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2024/05/21/2024-05-21-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2024/05/21/2024-05-21-audit/</guid>
      <description>Applications that utilize artifacts from the Kuksa project need to rely on the secure execution of these components. We are, therefore, happy to announce the publication of an external audit report carried out by Quarkslab. The audit was facilitated through OSTIF and the Eclipse Foundation and made possible by the funding the Eclipse Foundation received from the Alpha-Omega project.&#xA;The audit was scoped on the KUKSA databroker and the respective Python client SDK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUKSA at FOSDEM 2023</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2023/02/17/2023-02-17-fosdem2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2023/02/17/2023-02-17-fosdem2023/</guid>
      <description>KUKSA has been at the FOSDEM 2023 in Brussels. We show-cased how the Eclipse KUKSA project can help to leverage the advantages of a standardized description of vehicle signals&#xA;The talk presented the architectural answer given by the Eclipse KUKSA project to leverage the COVESA Vehicle Signal Specification inside a vehicle. It showed how to use KUKSA components to gather and transform the data from lower embedded layers in the vehicle, and providing them in a secure way to apps and services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUKSA CANOPi Prototyping platform for Software Defined Vehicle applications</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2022/03/24/2022-03-24-canopi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2022/03/24/2022-03-24-canopi/</guid>
      <description>If you have followed KUKSA over the last years you know the KUKSA OBD Prototyping Platform, a Raspberry CM3-based OBD dongle. Now we are proud to present the second iteration of the KUKSA hardware. As we are not limited to OBD anymore, a small rename was in order, so let&amp;rsquo;s welcome the&#xA;KUKSA CANOPi Platform a Rapid Prototyping Hardware for Software Defined Vehicle Applications. So what is new?&#xA;Two independent MCP251xFD based CAN-FD interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Eclipse Kuksa meets Eclipse SUMO [VIDEO]</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-when-kuksa-meets-sumo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-when-kuksa-meets-sumo/</guid>
      <description>This video features an approach for connecting the Eclipse SUMO track simulation with the open source connected vehicle ecosystem Eclipse Kuksa. More precisely, Eclipse SUMO is used to simulate traffic scenarios including microscopic properties like the position or emission. The generated data of each vehicle is then be sent to the message gateway of the Kuksa IoT Cloud platform and delegated to an according example service that consumes the data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Kuksa Hackathon 08.2018</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/08/30/2018-08-30-hack0818/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/08/30/2018-08-30-hack0818/</guid>
      <description>Hacking 3 Days @ IDiAL, FH-Dortmund, for Eclipse Kuksa Features 13 Hackers met in Dortmund on August, 28th until 30th of August to work on an end-to-end use case scenario along with new Eclipse Kuksa technologies. 20 CQs, 2 major GitHub pull-requests, and 21035 LOCs were the results. Of course, the LOCs also contain content from work prior to the Hackathon.&#xA;More precisely, the Eclipse Kuksa Appstore was migrated to an Eclipse HawkBit Server, that transmits applications wirelessly to an Eclipse HawkBit client running on a device (Raspberry Pi) that runs the Kuksa adapted AGL (Automotive Grade Linux + Kuksa technologies).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial Contributions</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/06/05/2018-06-05-initialcontribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/06/05/2018-06-05-initialcontribution/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Kuksa&amp;rsquo;s initial contribution was successfully submitted to the GitHub repositories. We are working on a roadmap to present planned activities for upcoming contributions. Apart from the three major Kuksa parts, i.e.,&#xA;kuksa.invehicle kuksa.cloud kuksa.ide additional repositories will cover specific use-cases, builds, tests, and other features within:&#xA;kuksa.apps kuksa.integration </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
