<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dissemination on Eclipse KUKSA</title>
    <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/categories/dissemination/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dissemination on Eclipse KUKSA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/categories/dissemination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kuksa.val for SCR Anti-Tampering in trucks [Talk]</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2021/06/24/2021-06-24-eclipsesaam-scr-anti-tampering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2021/06/24/2021-06-24-eclipsesaam-scr-anti-tampering/</guid>
      <description>The DIAS project used Eclipse KUKSA to detect tampering in the exhaust cleaning system of a modern truck. Modern internal combustion engines have several advanced exhaust treatment systems to meet emission standards and legislation. In case of Selective Catalytic Reduction (SCR) for diesel engines, a catalyst (“AdBlue®”) is used as consumable. This incurs costs for the operator of diesel vehicles and provides an incentive to unlawfully circumvent those systems.
The talk presents how the Eclipse KUKSA stack has been used to realize an anti-tampering system for commercial heavy-duty trucks exhaust systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eclipse Kuksa.val DBC Feeder Demo [Video]</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2020/08/18/2020-08-18-dbc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2020/08/18/2020-08-18-dbc/</guid>
      <description>Eclipse Kuksa.val DBC Feeder Demo [Video] This demo showcases the features of the kuksa.val (https://github.com/eclipse/kuksa.val) server.
While the automotive world is full of standards, there are not a lot of useful standards for an I(o)T world. Useful here means
Standardize on semantics, not technology only Usable across vendors, by anyone (car manufacturers, suppiers, aftermarket, third parties) Building on, or interacting with, common IT technologies One of the more useful approaches in this context is the Genivi Vehicle signal specification (VSS) (https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Eclipse Kuksa for Connected Vehicle Services [Video]</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2020/01/21/2020-01-21-eclipsecon19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2020/01/21/2020-01-21-eclipsecon19/</guid>
      <description>EclipseCon Europe 2019 Presentation: Using Eclipse Kuksa for Connected Vehicle Services &amp;hellip; is presented by project comitters and contributers at the EclispeCon Europe 2019:
EclipseCon Europe 2019 Interview: APPSTACLE &amp;amp; Eclilpse Kuksa </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuksa IDE [Video]</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/12/20/2019-12-20-idevideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/12/20/2019-12-20-idevideo/</guid>
      <description>Kuksa IDE Video published ITEA Article on 0.1.0 Release ITEA published a news article on Kuksa 0.1.0 at https://itea3.org/news/itea-appstacle-project-announces-eclipse-kuksa-platform-for-car-to-car-to-cloud.html
Kuksa 0.2.0 Release postponed to January 2020 Since minor organizational matters are still ongoing, we need to postpone Eclipse Kuksa 0.2.0 release to January 2020. Stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuksa IDE VSCE now available</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/12/13/2019-12-13-vsmarketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/12/13/2019-12-13-vsmarketplace/</guid>
      <description>Kuksa IDE Extension published to Visual Studio Code Marketplace Today, the Eclipse Kuksa team successfully published the latest Kuksa.IDE-VSCE at the Visual Studio Code marketplace. This Visual Studio Code Extension (VSCE) provides several commands to ease application development, docker image generation, and the transmission to an existing Eclipse Kuksa Appstore. More information can be found here. Download the Eclipse Kuksa IDE VSCE at the official VSCode marketplace now for free. The extension can be further used along with Eclipse Theia and Eclipse Che as part of an online IDE based on kubernetes and docker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Questionnaire</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/12/11/2019-12-11-questionaire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/12/11/2019-12-11-questionaire/</guid>
      <description>Help us with your feedback to further develop Eclipse Kuksa .. &amp;hellip; take a few moments as a developer to give us feedback from our ecosystem: In-Vehicle, Cloud, and IDE via https://forms.gle/XbhaugGQexb4pexi9
Thank you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APPSTACLE F2F Meeting &amp; Hackathon @ Netas, Istanbul, Turkey</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/09/19/2019-09-19-netas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/09/19/2019-09-19-netas/</guid>
      <description>The APPSTACLE project members and Eclipse Kuksa developers met in mid September 2019 to work on common challenges, release planning, documentation, and specifically technologies around the Eclipse Kuksa Appstore. Many issues could be resolved and the path to Eclipse Kuksa 0.1.0 looks promising!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summerschool FH-Dortmund - Automotive Stream</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/07/05/2019-07-05-summerschool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/07/05/2019-07-05-summerschool/</guid>
      <description>On regular basis, Dortmund University of Applied Sciences and Arts (Germany) organizes a one week summer school for students with various streams to choose from. As part of the automotive stream, Eclipse Kuksa technologies have been presented and students could get their hands on
the Eclipse Kuksa OBD dongle used in a real car scenario applications installed via the Appstore the Eclipse Kuksa Rover running AGL or Raspbian with the Eclipse Kuksa in-vehicle layers the new Eclipse Kuksa IDE for a simplified deployment of applications and cloud services and more&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Otokar Hatti</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/02/15/2019-02-15-otokar-magazin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2019/02/15/2019-02-15-otokar-magazin/</guid>
      <description>The Turkish consortium composed an article which is published in the monthly public magazine “Otokar Hattı” (“Otokar Production Line” in English).
Check it out page 6-7, of the following pdf file: Otokar Hatti.
The article is in Turkish
Erdem Ergen KoçSistem </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECE2018: Automotive meets IoT: Innovating your Future Vehicle</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/10/24/2018-10-24-ece2018-automotive-meets-iot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/10/24/2018-10-24-ece2018-automotive-meets-iot/</guid>
      <description>Sebastian Schildt (Robert Bosch GmbH) made a very interesting and well received presentation of the Kuksa project at EclipseCon Europe 2018.
Check it out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon Europe and ESE Kongress events</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/10/22/2018-10-22-ece1018ese1218/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 12:13:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/10/22/2018-10-22-ece1018ese1218/</guid>
      <description>EclipseCon France 2018 Eclipse Kuksa and its latest development activities will be presented along with the talk Automotive meets IoT: Innovating your Future Vehicle at EclipseCon Europe 2018 in Ludwigsburg, Germany.
Embedded Software Engineering Kongress 2018 In addition to the EclipseCon Europe event, you can join us at the ESE Kongress in Sindelfingen, Germany, on December, 6th. The talk Überwindung der Silos – Revolution für vernetzte Fahrzeuge, that means &amp;lsquo;Overcoming the Silos - Revolution for Connected Vehicles&amp;rsquo;, will be held at 16:45 o&amp;rsquo;clock (4:45pm) and will cover both a generic as well as detailed descriptions of the three Eclipse Kuksa platforms (a) In-Vehicle, (b) IDE, and ( c) Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon France 2018 interview</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/09/18/2018-09-18-ecf2018-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/09/18/2018-09-18-ecf2018-interview/</guid>
      <description>Interview with Robert Höttger (Fachhochschule Dortmund - University of Applied Science and Arts). Robert presented the recent news about the APPSTACLE project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EclipseCon France participation</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/06/18/2018-06-18-ecf2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2018/06/18/2018-06-18-ecf2018/</guid>
      <description>EclipseCon France 2018 Eclipse Kuksa was presented at EclipseCon France 2018 along with the research booth, the research community&amp;rsquo;s pitch session, a regular talk hold by Tobias Rawald and Robert Hoettger, and an interview about the motivation, goals, and the current state of Eclipse Kuksa.
https://twitter.com/phkrief/status/1007266197820329984
https://twitter.com/phkrief/status/1006833646119018496
https://twitter.com/phkrief/status/1006835234669842432</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oulanka Project Meeting</title>
      <link>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2017/10/26/2017-10-26-oulanka/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eclipse-kuksa.github.io/kuksa-website/blog/2017/10/26/2017-10-26-oulanka/</guid>
      <description>At the project meeting in Oulanka, Finnland, the APPSTACLE consortium collected and coordinated a variety of topics to work on in the upcoming time. Use-case scenarios, in-vehicle development activities, network protocols, cloud infrastructure, security demands, dissemination and exploitation and other topics were in focus for the project partners. The various discussions, cooperations, ideas, and further activities were defined in order to set the basis to reach the goals of APPSTACLE and form Eclipse Kuksa, i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
